let's look at the solution to our n
module redundancy quiz where we had
three computers that are totally
identical on the same desk and we use
them as a three modular redundant system
and the question is what type of event
can we always overcome a single alpha
particle strike is going to affect only
a single processor and that means that
the two computers that are not affected
by this will still agree
a building collapse
will either be another building and not
affect anything but if it is the
building in which these systems are then
the building collapse is probably going
to destroy all three computers so we
cannot tolerate this type of event
earthquake
is going to do a similar thing and a
mistake in processor design because the
three are identical
if there is a mistake in processor
design it's going to affect all three
processors at the same time so again we
cannot tolerate this
so as you can see
replicating the hardware with identical
hardware and in an identical location
only really ensures that we can survive
something like a particle strike if we
wanted to tolerate earthquakes and
building collapses we would need to
geographically distribute these three
computers if we want to tolerate a
mistake in processor design we would
need to use three computers with
different processors
so the n module redundancy
doesn't really guard against these types
of faults
unless the modules are in different
places
and of different designs